bayrozgar.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy

Bayrozgar.com cares about your privacy.

Bayrozgar.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and strives to provide a safe, secure user experience. The information we provide in the Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how Bayrozgar.com uses your information and the choices you have for protecting it.  
By accessing or using Bayrozgar.com, you agree to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use Bayrozgar.com.

**Personal Information**  
"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information. However you can browse Bayrozgar.com’s publically accessible pages without revealing any of your contact information.   
When you visit Bayrozgar.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all of our users. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. Some third party toolbars use persistent cookies to save your login information, these toolbars are in no way associated with Bayrozgar.com.  
In our online registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your name, your email address, your gender, and your date of birth, your location details and some optional details about yourself. These details are available to you anytime, and are capable of being corrected, altered or updated through your "Profile" page. Please note that this personal information is necessary for the employers to connect with you and send you interview requests.

We internally use personal information of our users to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout.   
By registering on the website you acknowledge and agree that the profile data and other postings that you provide, including sensitive personal data, may be accessed by Employers from Pakistan as well as abroad.

**Disclosure of your information**  
We do not sell or rent out any personal information about you to any third party. However Bayrozgar.com would cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law if we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served.  
You should not enter any personal information such as your email address or contact address and phone number in your profile sections such as “Professional Summary” and “Professional Experience”. Please note that these sections are accessible publically and are meant for Employers to search for suitable candidates for their jobs.

You may not use other users' information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who misuse other users' information or who otherwise violates the Terms of use.

**Inactivity**  
You may choose to leave your account dormant for an unlimited period of time.

**Note to minors**  
We do not knowingly market to or encourage children, minors or anyone under the age of 18 to use our services and we request that children do not submit information to us.

**Control of your password**  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Bayrozgar.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
